the Wistly Exitment Blast Week, I just forgot to put that it was chapter 2.
I just gave you a section.
Excuse me.
Warrens.
I.
13.
Regarding the adoption that we're proposed, social media policy.
For use by city, social media, administrative.
Um, this is the much anticipated social media policy that, um, by.
Action of the city council of the governing body.
Um, creates within our social media platforms.
A limited public form.
So, a public forum, you cannot, um, control the speech in any way.
With a limited public forum, we talked about this before, as long as the policy is clear.
And it is important equally among all participants in that platform.
You can limit the speech to whatever the content of the social media side is.
Well, if the lease department posts about, um, a given topic, a case or, um,
or, and it's something that they've done, or they've posted a funny meme or whatever.
And you get on and want to, um, use that as your platform to voice your opinion about the war and
Gaza.
You would not be allowed to do that.
You would have to stay on topic with whatever the post is.
If you're talking about heritage best, we're talking about heritage best.
If we're talking about, um, the morning brew, we're talking about morning brew.
We're not talking about world affairs.
Are you guilty?
Yes.
I mean, they would, and the comments would never be deleted because they are subject to open records request.
They would just be, um, turned off our muted.
Yeah.
This is something they have to post on their social media page.
Right.
So, under purpose, the little block at the end of section one.
That would have to go on the about pay.
The, um, professor and, um, more of it that we can say.
salted with on this matter, let's ski with her name. She said that you would need to put that on your
about page and be very clear that this is our intent and then basically you just have to enforce it
among all people. So if the mayor gets on and starts talking about dollars, I won't work talking about
heritage, but then we have to shut in up. I'm sure you can do that. Amazing. Amazing.
And in peachy. It has the equally enforced health. No, this seems like it's geared towards like
sites, not so much as commenters. So I mean, no, it's not like I talked about it anymore. Well, it's for
like I may not have the responsibility to go into it. Oh, yes, but I'm talking about like that.
So this is just a disclaimer that if there is an official, say there's an emergency situation
and you need to get the information out, the city website will still be the official means of communication.
That way we're not on the hook for not having whatever the information is posted on all of our Facebook
pages because we have a lot of them.
I mean the alternative would be just shut off comments.
You might be probably, you might be your city post.
I can lock it and share it and all that, but there's no...
I know I personally have a lot of people reach out and they're like,
Does this city support so-and-so?
Because they don't ever do anything about this comment,
and I'm like, well, has it right now, we don't have a policy in place, but we're working.
All right.
Well, I mean, I'd like to make this up.
I'm willing to speak back on it, because being on both sides of the aisle,
especially as a reporter, like to understand the importance of free speech
in the life of the violation and not trying to cross boundaries, but also a link.
We have to check ourselves, we have to check our community,
and our, you know, the city, especially from anything that we don't want to be involved.
I might have told me to direct a policy.
Yeah, I agree.
Well, it's exactly being done.
If you look at other city sites, it's exactly being, of course.
So, these policies are in place for a reason.
And if you get more of that...
I think I'd recommend that we table this until the group can get together and come up with a plan to make sure we implement it, right, because I'm 100% on board.
We need a policy and we need to be able to police the things that are making us look bad as a city from that perspective.
But I agree that we need to make sure we do it right.
So Tyler, what does that look like from your perspective? Do you put a subcommittee together and come up with an implementation plan?
That would be fine.
I mean, one of my concerns is like who's the kind of one before.
I mean, I just said, you know, if you fill an issue, you know, then you need to bring that up to the department head.
I mean, you know, if that's not if the situation is not situated, if it's used me, you know, you bring it up to the director and then I mean, you become the after that.
I mean, if it's not fixed and you just come to the city manager and the city attorney.
I mean, you know, because she was worried about the accountability that she had.
But if we're going to run a Facebook page, the administrator has to accept responsibility for that.
Sure.
And then there's me called the pages are right.
Nobody is in direct.
We're going to make that page.
Or somebody tells something that I make the lead somebody from the city attorney.
And we did, and we did, and we did take out the part that said that the communications manager
is responsible for oversight.
I think we'd put the each, and my thoughts would be great.
So we don't have a problem with what policy looks like, this implementation.
Right.
Okay.
So we can put it on the point.
We can actually improve policy and then turn it over Tyler on the implementation.
Yeah.
Can we get with that?
The only one like I questioned before, and it was that four, seven, four, seven, four, seven,
four, seven, four.
So let's take solicitation of commerce, or advertising, particularly promotion or endorsement.
And the one thing you see that are the pages that I see that I'm harming are mainstream.
Well, it's not intended to, I mean, if they're not to city science or supposed to be exempt, we can, but we can clarify that.
When it goes into, including promotion or endorsement, I feel like that hinder our mainstream program solely.
Is that specifically talking about people trying to sell things on our,
Well, no, it says, but it says, including promotion.
Right.
I read it that way for solicitations of commerce.
They're not looking to solicit, exchange of commerce.
But as soon as it added the including promotion or endorsement, they are promoting and endorsing businesses.
I think that can be reverted to fix the attack.
Because I think the intent is not to do what you're saying.
I think the intent is to prevent just regular Joe from.
Come visit my side.
I sell, beaded jewelry, and it's really a scam that takes you to a site where they still your identity.
You can lose your kidneys.
Yeah.
I wasn't going to get a lot of that.
I was going to get a lot of that.
So, you've got something to do.
I'm going to do this.
I don't know.
We wanted to read it.
So, I just wanted to add a bit.
I'm going to send four, four, seven, four.
And we're going to like, we're also going to say, because it's especially where you're getting
that jewelry.
I just don't want it.
We could even add them.
I mean, we can start some of the laws.
This is excluding city and the entity's department.
I want you to just say solicitation of non-approved entities.
I want you to say solicitation of non-approved entities.
But not on and take my non-operative.
Do you have any of those signs?
You can't.
I mean, I just, for the first time,
when I become out of policy,
doesn't say that I need it to go.
Because the go-wars case scenario,
if you have somebody that's getting trouble
because they,
the handle, social media post,
correctly, or how we feel like you should have been handled.
And they say, well, nobody told me,
what do we have to fall back?
Because they could say, well, it's not in policy.
Nobody told them what do we have to say?
Do we have to say, okay, you weren't formed?
Is that part of the role?
Yeah, I mean, we just have people sign
of that there where the social media post.
I mean, we sign many other things, you know, like sexual harassment.
Yeah, we're seats.
Yeah.
If I, I would even go a separate,
or decide that if they have questions,
they have the opportunities to speak with the city manager,
city attorney, or whoever.
What's the public translation of that look like,
as well?
Or the transition?
Or, post something publicly stating that there's empty new laws,
or being able to...
Well, there's a building about,
if you can't talk about it.
Yeah.
Or will we post something like that?
Well, if I had probably both,
I mean, you would want to draw as much attention to it as possible.
Well, that's the only about on every page city space,
and then every city page and on each post as well.
Well, probably, yes.
That's more of the implementation.
But I would say, make it as public as possible.
Yeah.
No second.
Can we approve subject to that one?
We've been to a minute to item 41474,
or, or, sort of, re-learning a review of 41474.
I second.
Second.
Sorry.
We're going to do that.
We'll go to the next generation later, right?
We'll fill this wall.
Actually, they get back until...
We'll put it on our, we'll put it on the Facebook page,
and then we'll start going through the people that post
to make sure they're properly trained.
So, before anybody takes any action that my go against,
they'll be trained on what action they're allowed to take,
not allowed to take.
Perfect.
I mean, I have to want to hate post and anything on Facebook,
so it's 2.30 in the morning and Derek are opposed to,
and that we have a power outage or whatever,
and I'm thinking, like, I have them from the right page,
and I'll post, build everything correctly.
You know, and so.
Go, go, hi.
14, the new business, if any, that's been because the business is pushing this into the 15 staff reports,
16, American Council, Reaville, 17, see you, Madder, BJ.
I just think everybody will put with a rodeo, and then also to serve everybody knows.
We're posting a HR position, and this week, so if you may know, as you may, this may interest it,
so Cindy has told everyone that she's interviewing someone next year, so this person will be hopefully the one that takes over for Cindy.
Let's make the motion we not approve.
We don't miss Cindy a lot, but that's not to make everybody aware.
So, retirement.
Congratulations, Cindy.
Hey, he told me to do it.
Thank you, Ryan.
That's all I have.
Thank you, Jeremy.
Motion.
He's back.
Hi.
Joe's.
Hi, words.
Hi.